

MUHAMMAD MUSTAQEEM

UI/UX DESIGN



Portfolio Website

ABOUT US

Hey I'm a ui/ux designer engineer with great of experience in understanding and designing digital products from concept ideas to production. I work with my clients to help them create web apps and mobile apps from the ground up or to help them solve business problems through visual and usability improvements.

- **■** 03067101225, 03423510876
- ☐ m-mustaqeem@outlook.com
- **Q** 478 airline main blvd lahore

EDUCATION

INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

— 2014 - 2018

Bahauddin Zakariya University, Multan

FSC PRE ENGINEERING

— 2011 – 2014

B.I.S.E FSD

MATRIC SCIENCE GROUP

— 2009 – 2011

B.I.S.E FSD

CERTIFICATIONS

UI/UX DESIGNER

Treehouse online Cources
Jan 2019 to July 2019

U

Treehouse online Cources
May 2019 to July 2019

WORK EXPERIENCE

TOTAL 3+ YEARS

UX Consultant Citrok Lahore — Feb 2022 - Present

In my position in the company as a UX consultant, I work on different kinds of products like CMS, SAAS, App design, and website + responsive solutions.

UX Designer Bitsclan Solution Lahore — Feb 2019 - Apr 2019

My position in the company was as a senior UI/UX designer, I did many projects like Elevatyx website design + wireframe, Kelger Management website design+Develop Front end only, DrGlow website, MFC App, and KFC App.

UI/UX Designer

Xaavia Studios Lahore — May 2020 - Jan 2022 · 1 yr 9 mos

I joined the company as a UI/UX Designer. I designed and created a complete professional branding suite for one of their client mentioned as Blackstone including the logo, Website design, Marketing material, and Application graphics as well. I also designed the entire wireframe of the Text Neck App launched by Moltyfoam and Burnsroad House Website.

UI/UX Designer

Bitsclan Solution Lahore — Apr 2019 - Sep 2019

After 3 months I was promoted to UI/UX designer. I designed a Urtasker website, which was an e-commerce solution, I also designed the wireframe as well as the entire design. Including some marketplace websites and wireframe designs.

Graphic Designer Bitsclan Solution Lahore — Feb 2019 - Apr 2019

I will join this company as a Junior Graphic designer, I did many projects like logo designing, banner animation, etc.

SKILLS





